#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

# Md Rezaul Islam



Address | House 62, Road 18, Sector 11, Uttara, Dhaka, BD 1230

Phone | +88 01738157678

E-Mail | rezabdt@gmail.com

Portfolio | http://rezabdt.github.io/

1 LinkedIn | https://www.linkedin.com/in/rezabdt/

Skype | rezabdt007

Gender: Male | Date Of Birth: 17/09/1991 | Nationality: Bangladeshi

## CAREER SUMMARY

I'm a Digital Marketer. SEO, SMM & Web Development with Over 5 Years of Experience. Experienced with All Stages of The Marketing Cycle for Product Promotion & Also CMS Developer.

- 5 Years of Professional Experience with 10+ Years of Marketing skills
- Marketing Experience in Google Adwords, Facebook Ads, ASO
   & All Mainstream Social Media. Also Email Marketing.
- Analytical Skill to Understand Market.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Jun 2019 -Dec 2020

# Digital Marketing Executive | Full Time

Alt Fix Ltd. | Baridhara DOSH, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Sales & Marketing | Image Post Production

### Responsibilities:

- Digital Marketing
- Web Development & Maintenance
- Graphics Design

#### Oct 2017 - Present

### Team Lead | Part-Time

WeblyWork | Lalmonirhat, Rangpur, Bangladesh

Sales & Marketing | Software & ITES

# Responsibilities:

- Digital Marketing
- Android Development, Front-End & Back-End Development
- Leadership Team of 5
- Development & Maintaining Projects for Clients

### Apr 2017 - May 2017

### Lead Trainer | Contract

LEDP | Lalmonirhat, Rangpur, Bangladesh

Digital Marketing | Training Course

#### Responsibilities:

- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Social Media Marketing (SMM)
- Email Marketing
- Freelancing Marketplace

## July 2013 - Present Freelancer | Part-Time

Fiverr & Upwork | fiverr.com, upwork.com Sales & Marketing | Digital Marketing

Responsibilities:

Social Media Marketing (SMM)

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

## May 2010 – June 2013 Marketing Executive | Full Time

RangpurSource | Rangpur, Bangladesh Sales & Marketing | Digital Marketing Responsibilities:

- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Social Media Marketing (SMM)
- Email Marketing

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## Jan 2010 - Dec 2012 Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com)

Business Studies | National University

Result | 2nd Division

## Jan 2007 - Dec 2009 Higher Secondary Certificate (H.S.C)

Commerce | Lalmonirhat Govt. College, Lalmonirhat, Rangpur, Bangladesh

Result | GPA 3.00 out of 5.00

# Jan 2005 - Dec 2006 Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C)

Science | Bangladesh Railway Children Park High School, Lalmonirhat, Rangpur,

Bangladesh

Result | GPA 3.94 out of 5.00

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Mother Tongue(s) Bangla

English

Other Language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
Average	Average	Average	Average	Average

Communication Skills

I have gathered good client communication skills during my various project life cycle.

Organizational / Managerial Skills

- Leadership Team of 5
- Project Management skills at a present organization.

## Digital Skills

Digital	Web Development	Graphics	Apps	Problem
Marketing		Design	Development	Solving
EXPERT	AVERAGE	AVERAGE	BELOW	BELOW

Certifications

**Learning and Earning Development Project, ICT Division** 

Course: Digital Marketing Duration: 300 Hours

**Technical Skills** 

SEO, SMM, Email Marketing, Google Ads, Facebook Ads, ASO, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, Joomla, Android Studio, Ads Networks, Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, After Effect,

Domain, Hosting, Ubuntu Server.

References

Md. Eyasin Ali Sarker | CARE Bangladesh | M&E Manager -Program Quality, SHOUHARDO III Program RAOWA Complex, VIP Road, Mohakhali, Dhaka-1206, Bangladesh

Phone:+880-2-9889009, Ext 221 | Cell +880 1718595626 | email: eyasinali.sarker@care.org

**Arman Hossain** 

Mobile Application Developer, Shakti Foundation, Mirpur 1, Dhaka, Bangladesh Mobile: 01918-304040 Email: armans.postbox@gmail.com

I do hereby declare that all the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Respectfully yours,

Md Rezaul Islam

Last Modified: 01 / 06 / 2021